Bara Burū 1.00

© 2016 Kagesan

Music engine: PSGlib by sverx
Thanks to psidum and Calindro for testing



Seemingly out of the blue, vile sea creatures start attacking peaceful coastal
towns, as a strange tower-like structure rises from the icy depths of the ocean.
Guide master ninjas Bara and Burū through thirty levels of the mysterious tower
and vanquish the evil that dwells within!

Controller 1 starts 1-player game, controller 2 starts 2-player game.

How to play:

1. Slash enemies to stun them.
2. Push stunned enemies into walls.
3. Collect bonus.